digitalseoservice.com 2016-10-23

# Privacy Policy | Acquire online SEO & SMO service supplier | Digitalseoservice

## Privacy Policy

At [www.digitalseoservice.com](http://www.digitalseoservice.com/) we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by [www.digitalseoservice.com](http://www.digitalseoservice.com/) and how we use it.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [www.digitalseoservice.com](http://www.digitalseoservice.com/) makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[www.digitalseoservice.com](http://www.digitalseoservice.com/) does not use cookies.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
